Wertheimer, Barbara Additional Files 5736
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Women and The Law 74M040L, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Women in the Workforce 74M039L, 1962-1972 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- Leila Raquel Arjona Bi-Lingual Teacher, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Daralee Schulman Stress Instruction, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Short Courses, 1979-1980 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Career Development, 1979-1980 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Public Speaking Metro Postal 1079 - 11/13/79, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Writing for Trade Unionists Metro Postal 10/9 - 11/13/79, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Sexual Harassment November 9, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- NCWW:- Notes (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Budget National Commission on Working Women, 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Business Woman Traveler Expenses, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Ford Foundation Invitational Conf. Proceedings Draft, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Correspondence - Re: Grant (Ford Foundation Personnel), 1979 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Correspondence Participants, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- National Conference for Univ. Labor, Ext Programs, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Draft Copy - Ford Proceedings, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Expenses Connected with 6/15 Ford/Cornell Conference, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Developing University and Union Labor Education for Trade Union Women, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Labor, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Institute for Education and Research on Women and work, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 19)
- Institute for Education and Research on Women and Work, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 20)
- Press Releases 1975 (Box 19, Folder 21)
- Information Cover Letter, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 22)
- S.S. Planning Meeting, 1981-1982 (Box 19, Folder 23)
- Labor Press Conference June 19, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 24)
- Northeastern Summer School Orono Maine, 7/19-24/1981 (Box 19, Folder 25)
- Effective Letter Writing, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 26)
- Union Women and Political Process 75M231L, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 27)
- 76M166L - Politics, 1976-1977 (Box 19, Folder 28)
- Winter '77, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 29)
- New Developments In EED Law, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 30)
- Winter 1977 (Box 19, Folder 31)
- Winter 1977 (Box 19, Folder 32)
- Fall 1976 (Box 19, Folder 33)
- Women's Studies, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Effective Speaking (Box 20, Folder 2)
- In-Service Winter '77, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Fall '76, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Summary Fall '76, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Flight Attendants F76 76M148L, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Spring '76, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Summary Sp 76, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Summer '76, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- In-Service Programs Spring '76, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Confirmation of Registration, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Writing Fall 76 76M126L (Parker), 1976 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Collective Barg. F76 76M122L, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Spring '76, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Summary Fall '76, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Donna Mobley - Short course Eval. Political Process, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Occupational Health 76M002L, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Psychology of Leadership S76 76M019L, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Union Women's Program June 11, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- Short Courses 1979 Fall spring 80 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- Beginning Journalism ILGWU Local 155 3/1-4/5/79, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 21)
- Effective Speaking 3/5 - 4/9/79 Metro Postal, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 22)
- Beginning Journalism 3/5 - 4/9/79 Metro Postal, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 23)
- Working Women and the Law (Box 21, Folder 1)
- State-Wide Teachers' Meeting -July 27, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Evaluation Forms (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Maternity and Pregnancy Provisions 75M184L, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Grievances Women and Work, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Grievance Handling (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Mathematics of Work 76M003L, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Effective Speaking 75M008L, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Copyright Letters Reissued (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Copyright Permission Letters (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Copyright Orders Spring 1975 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Copyrights, 1974-1976 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Chancellor Wharton's Speech Press Release, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Board Meeting Roosevelt Hotel, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Women's Institute- Advisory Board of Director's Meeting - Biltmore Hotel March 8, 1979 Correspondence (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Advisory Board 3/8/79 Materials for Kit., 1979 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- 100 Years of Women, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Effective Speaking 3/10-4/21/79 Donna Mobley, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Public speaking RWDSU - Local 3 Donna Mobley, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Beginning Journalism January 8 - February 12 - 1979 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Journalism - Original Syllabus, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Beginning Journalism for Union Women, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Effective Letter- writing for Union Women - CWA (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Health and Safety, 1976-1978 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Teaching Methods and Techniques, 1976-1978 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Health Hazards and the White Collar Worker, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Union Safety and Health Committee (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Working women - Money Thursday - 5/4, 14, 18, 25; June 1, 8, 1978 Local 155 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Working Women + Money ILGWU - Local 91, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Working Women and Money, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Slaves: Hired Out Apprenticed (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Runaways - Underground RR. (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Industrial Slaves, 1942 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Black Workers/ Gen. Sht. Hist., 1865-1909 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Industrial Education (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Indenture, Hideout, Apprentice, 1865-1866 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Agriculture/Tenant Farm, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Slaves (Men), 1968 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Slaves (Women), 1937-1972 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Reconstruction: Impact on Blacks, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- West: Cowboys, Settlers etc. (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Knights of Labor (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Black Workers in Selected Cities 1865-1914 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Women - Black, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Blackson the War Front Civil War, 1917 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Cond. Of Negro During War/ Jobs Politics, 1863 (Box 23, Folder 16)
- Male Free Laborers, 1830-1840 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- Female Free Laborers (Box 23, Folder 18)
- Northern Negroes, 1820-1840 (Box 23, Folder 19)
- Negroes: Apprenticeship -Hire, 1834 (Box 23, Folder 20)
- Abolitionists, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 21)
- Colonization (Box 23, Folder 22)
- Turn of the Century and the World War 1 Era, 1900-1918 (Box 23, Folder 23)
- 1900's AFL Beginnings, 1900-1909 (Box 23, Folder 24)
- Before the 17th Century Background (Box 23, Folder 25)
- Women in the 17th Century (Box 23, Folder 26)
- 18th Century- Women in Work, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 27)
- 18th Century and Rev. War Activities, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 28)
- 18th Century Post Revolutionary, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 29)
- 18th Century Pioneer Women, 1953 (Box 23, Folder 30)
- Civil War and Status of Black Women, 1828-1869 (Box 23, Folder 31)
- Post Civil War and the National Labor Union, 1916-1965 (Box 23, Folder 32)
- 19th Century Textile Mills, 1915-1977 (Box 23, Folder 33)
- Master of Arts in the School of Education, 1959-1960 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Handbook for Consumer Counselors (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Women as Third-Party Neutrals: Gaining Acceptability, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Exploring the Arts; Handbook for Trade Union Program Planners (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Handbook for Consumer Counselors A Resource and Training Manual, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Handbook for Consumer Counselors, 1968-1970 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Labor Explores the Arts, 1974-1976 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Institute for Education and Research, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Institute for Education and Research on Women and Work, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Institute for Education and Research on Women and Work, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Institute for Education and Research on Women and Work, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Institute for Education and Research on Women and Work (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Institute for Education and Research on Women and Work, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Elizabeth Koontz, 1978-1979 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Course Outlines, 1971-1975 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Handbook for Consumer Relations, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 16)
- Misc. Papers, 1828-1853 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Coalition of Labor Union Women, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Formation of CLUW (Including Statements of Purpose), 1868 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- National CLUW Ed. Comm., 1976 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Oral Histories 1964-Now (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Speeches from CLUW Conferences, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- CLUW Resolutions and Objectives MADAR, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Empowerment "Ciders, Comm." CLUW, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- CLUW Cond. Dec. '75, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- CLUW Resolutions and Political Stands and Objectives Miller, 1979-1980 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Carnegie, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- CLUW Newsletters, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- CLUW - Local Chapters (NY, NJ, Long Island), 1981 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Other Unions and CLUW, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 14)
- Barbara's Notes on CLUW, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 15)
- NTUL - CLUW, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 16)
- CLUW - 1st Person, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 17)
- CLUW (Pre-CLUW Session July 1973) (Box 26, Folder 18)
- CLUW - Criticisms and Prospects for Future, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 19)
- CLUW General, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 20)